{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","address":"11831 E Seven Mile Rd. ","zipcode":"48205","owner":"Kanisha Greer","licenseNumber":"078742","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/29/2016","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000A82160632DC054C088E631D2A4374540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43836","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","inspectionDate":"2018-10-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"inspectionid":"43836","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"That allows food to be above 41 degrees f","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42267","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","inspectionDate":"2018-04-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"2","pfcount":"1","ccount":"6","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"6","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"inspectionid":"42267","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."}]},{"inspectionid":"40410","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","inspectionDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"3","pfcount":"5","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"8","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store under refrigeration."},{"inspectionid":"40410","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"38320","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","inspectionDate":"2017-03-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38320","inspectionDate":"3/15/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"38320","inspectionDate":"3/15/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"36717","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","inspectionDate":"2016-09-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36717","inspectionDate":"9/16/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"36717","inspectionDate":"9/16/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4772"}}